A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Office of the Vice President, Media Projects, Office Files of Andrea L. Taylor FA684
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence Files, 1993-1996; 7; 2.09 Cubic Feet 6 containers
  - 1995 Correspondence, 1995 January-March (Box 56, Folder 704-705)
    Don Adams, America's War on Poverty, Cornell F. Amaya, Sarah Ashton, Sharyn Bahn, Gilbert Bailon, Larry M. Bartels, Barbara Becker, Alison Bernstein, Susan Berresford, Dr. Ethel Rios de Betancourt, Sheila Biddle, Stewart Bird, Ray Blanco, Dr. Frank Bonilla, Claudia Bonn, Timothy Bork, Robert L. Brantley, Henry Breitrose, Melissa Burch, Patty Burness, H. Raymond Carby-Samuels II, Charles M. Carroll, Dr. Steven A. Channing, Jason C. Chapin, Linda S. Chapman, Martin Charlot, Christopher Charron, Christine Choy, Katie Cochran, Helen S. Cohen, Janet Cole, William Costello, Robert Curvin, Joan Dassin, Alan Dater, Gene A. Davis, Kenneth R. Day, Sandie de Freitas, Daniel del Solar, Jane M. de Vyver, John E. Echohawk, Dr. Patricia Edgar, Connie Field, Kevin Flattery, Shepard Forman, Martha Fowlkes, Wayne Fredericks, Maiya Furgason, Barry Gaberman, Shauna Garr, Peter Geithner, John Gerhart, Judith Ginsberg, Rajcomarie Gokul, Angela Goldberg, Betty Gowey, Slawomir Grunberg, Theodore J. Habarth, Lewis I. Haber, Nicole Haberland, Henry Hampton, Margaret Hempel, Kathryn High, Charles B. Hobson, Sam Hocking, Gill Holland, John Holler, Julian Hollick, Lynn Huntley, Sandy Itkoff, Melanie Judd, Lillian Jimenez, Sherry Jones, Gayle Anne Kelley, Marge Kennedy, Fran Korten, Polly Kosko, George A. Krimsky, Madison Lacy, Tom Laney, Robert Lamb, Ruby Lerner, Delano E. Lewis, Allie Light, Richard L. Loveless, Theodora Lurie, Joe MacDonald, JoAnna Baldwin Mallory, Richard A. Martin, Warren Mead, Greg Mendelwager, Lisa Mensah, Roberta A. Merkel, George L. Miles, Frank Millspaugh, Thandika Mkandawire, Nancy E. Monson, Janice Molnar, Cornelius Moore, James Morgese, Jonathan Moyo, Marjorie Muecke, Donald P. Mullally, Molly M. Multedo, James Briggs Murray, Frances McElroy, Marika Naaris, Helen Neuborne, Rebecca Nichols, Polycarp Omolo Ochilo, Charles Okigbo, April A. Oliver, Melanie Beth Oliviero, Michael O'Callaghan, Gerald Orange, Gail Pellett, Janice Petrovich, Sharon Philippart, Lyle Poitra, Debra Reber, Terra Renee, Madeleine Richport-Haley, Dale Riehl, Victoria Rodriguez-Thiessen, Audrey Simon, Gerald Rosenberg, Jack Rushen, Calvin Skaggs, Stephen L. Salyer, Ellen Schneider, Diana Schulz, Jules Schwerin, Victor Seltzer, Kent M. Sidel, William H. Siemering, Arvind Singhal, Anna Deavere Smith, Marcia Smith, Vanessa H. Smith, Richard Snibble, Marjorie Spiegel, Rosalind G. Stark, Ann Stock, Hugh Taylor, Kerwin Tesdell, Amanda Theunissen, Helen Thorington, Sharon Tiller, Ken Tiven, Mustapha Tlili, Peter Tooke, Eva Toth, Mercedes Lynn de Uriarte, Angela Dalle Vacche, Christine Vincent, Philip F. Viola, Torben Vosbein, Anna S. Wadia, Dr. Kim Walker, Frank Warner, Mitsuru Watanabe, Roger Weisberg, Cooper Wright, Lynn Walker, Stanley A. Zuckerman
  - 1995 Correspondence, 1995 April-June (Box 56, Folder 706-707)
    Tabatha Aboumrad, Victoria Adams, Steven Alves, David Appleby, Vera Aronow, Michael Bailey, Ludgar K. Balan, Anthony Bannon, Zita Barrueto, Donna Bellorado, Dr. Georgette F. Bennett, Dr. William Berkowitz, Gordon Berlin, Susan Berresford, Regine Beyer, Sheila Biddle, Timothy Bork, Timothy Bowser, Ellen S. Buchwalter, Seipati Bulane-Hopa, Dee Burton, Michael Camerini, Bruce Campbell, Sharron Cannon, Stephanie J. Castillo, Ward B. Chamberlin, Jr., Debra Chaplan, Gail Christian, Sandy Close, Janet Close, Larry Cox, Bill Curry, Robert Curvin, Jane M. de Vyver, Irv Drasnin, Frances D'Souza, Arvella E. Edwards, Jerry Ehrlich, Jan Olaf Fallman, Maureen Fiedler, Charles M. Firestone, Shepard Forman, Martha Fowlkes, Thomas E. Frank, Jon Funabiki, Rosemary Garner, Julie Garrett, Khari M. Garvin, Karl Geiringer, Peter Geithner, Leslie George, Michele Gisser, June I. Givanni, Joseph Glymph, Nicholas Gottlieb, Denise A. Greene, Cheryl Grills, Joan Grossman, Martine Haas, Nicole Haberland, Barbara A. Hall, Joan Hall, Daniel Hardy, Christie Hauck, Terry Spencer Hesser, Henry Hampton, Roland S. Homet, Laurie Ihm, Mahnaz Ispahani, Jan Jaffe, Vera Jelinek, Pamela K. Jennings, Richard Joseph, Catherine Joyce, Dr. Alexandra Juhasz, Natalia Kanem, Isao Kawasaki, Kakuna Kerina, Michael C. Kessen, Larry Kirkman, Anita Klever, Polly S. Kosko, Bill Kovach, Alexis Kravitz, George A. Krimsky, Daresha Kyi, Majie Lavergne, Margaret Lazarus, Ruby Lerner, Charles Lewis, Delano E. Lewis, Charmaine Lewis, Aaron Levine, Evelyn Lindsey, James Lipscomb, Clarence Lilley, Richard L. Loveless, Kathleen Mackay, Torey Malatia, Ann Walker Marchant, Richard A. Martin, Lorraine Maughlin, Luke Mellon, Lisa Mensah, Roberta A. Merkel, Gabrielle Micallef, Janice Molnar, Cornelius Moore, Marjorie Muecke, Claus Mueller, Aubrey McCutcheon, Gail D. McClure, Ceasar McDowell, Dirk McLean, Carolyn Naifeh, Helen Neuborne, Maria Nicolo, Henri Norris, Amram E. Nowalk, Hamid Nowlana, Walter C. Oberndorf, Ed Offutt, Chuck Olin, Jeffrey Olson, Cindy Oster, Jeanne Paynter, Robert J. Petrick, Katherine Petrie, Janice Petrovich, Per Pinstrup-Anderson, Michael L. Privitera, Mike Rabehl, Tricia Regan, Elizabeth D. Richter, Jonathan Robinson, Thomas L. Robertson, Sherry Rockey, Rocky Mountain Media Watch, Victoria Rodriguez-Thiessen, George Sachs, Roy J. Saldana, Marla J. Sammuli, Judy Samuelson, Elisa Scatena, Irwin Schneiderman, John Shanahan, Robert J. Shuman, Keith Shiri, Margarita Sierra, Jaanus Silla, Audrey Simon, Mike Sirek, Beck Sloca, Anna Deveare Smith, Marcia Smith, Susan Steiner, Michael Stock, M. L. Snijders, Eric Swanson, Helen Thorington, John Tidwell, W. J. Tigner, Sandy Tolan, Roberta Tross, Orlando Martin Vega, Christine Vincent, Lisa Vives, Michael Wasserman, Karen E. Watson, Hugh Watt, Veta Weir, Marilyn Weiner, Roger Weisberg, Marc Weiss, Robert Wesley, Ernest J. Wilson, Ginger Wolf, Jessica Yu, June Zetlin, Bert Zimmerman
  - 1995 Correspondence, 1995 July-September (Box 56, Folder 708, Box 57, Folder 709)
    Jean S. Aigner, Angela J. S. Alexander, Linda Bawden Allen, Alia Arasoughty, Ann Armstrong, Sarah Ashton, Gina Bailey, Brenda J. Ball, Anita Bennett, Susan Berresford, Sheila Biddle, Daniel Birman, Robert Bjorklund II, Jeanne Blake, Tim Bork, Alexandra Branyon, Marty Callaghan, Benoit Caron, Carmen Coustaut, Larry Cox, James R. Craig, Jennifer Croft, Humphrey Davies, Kristina Davies, Stewart Dickson, Darlene Dowling, Mandla W. Dude, Willie Edwards, Michael Elasmar, Kate Weckesser English, Jodie Evans, Theresa A. Fayko-Murphy, Meir Fenigstein, Randy Fertel, Carol Forshee, Curtis Fox, Kevin E. Fry, Barry Gaberman, Janet Gardner, Lloyd Garrison, Peter Geithner, Nina Gibans, Norman Goodman, Rhoda Grauer, Jennifer Greisz, Daniel W. Grieve, Timothy Gunn, Mable Haddock, S. M. Mazharul Haque, Peter Harris, Robert S. Hawkins, Richard D. Heffner, George F. Huggins, Marilyn Hunt, Jan Jaffe, Pete Jacques, Arthur C. Jones, Peter Katona, Joel Katz, Gayle Anne Kelley, Marcia Killingsworth, Nate Kohn, Karen Kramer, Madison D. Lacy, Frederic Laffont, Debra Latham, James R. Lee, Paul Lee, Barbara R. Levin, Regge Life, Michael Lipsky, Joseph Lovett, Gregory MacDonald, Tim Marema, Rebecca Marvil, Michelle A. Matterre, Janice Molnar, Gean Moreno, Lael Morgan, Marjorie Muecke, Tim McInnes, William McKeever, Len McClure, Native American Film and Video Festival, Rebecca Nichols, Amram E. Nowak, Edward L. O'Brien, Matthew Palm, Gay Iris Parker, Jeanne Parr, Drew Pearson, Gail Pellett, Vera S. Proctor, Wendy D. Puriefoy, Sharon Remedios, Jeffery Richards, Elizabeth Richter, Beatrice Righi, Theodora Lurie, Victoria Rodriguez-Thiessen, Pat Rubino, Association Sarajevo, Elisa Scatena, Gabriella Schang, Ned Schnurman, Jill Schoolman, Noel Schwerin, Joshua Seftel, Ahmed Seifelnasr, Bravo-Ramos Sergio, Nancy H. Shanks, Barbara Shelly, Leila Siller, Kevin Singer, Hedrick L. Smith, Paul Solman, Ruth C. Sproat, Rhea Stein, Joseph Stimpfl, Franklin Thomas, Shari Lynn Verona, Christine Vincent, Mark Walstrom, Jennifer Watts, Jeanette A. Watts, Elizabeth Weatherford, Peter C. White, Jim Whitman, Kay Wise, Leslie R, Wolfe, Pedro Zurita, Steve Zwerling
  - 1995 Correspondence, 1995 October-December (Box 57, Folder 710-711)
    Alice Allen, Sarah Ashton, Helen Brew, Maria Bakkalapulo, Stephen Balkam, Reggie Banks, Hajrudin Beca, Edgar Beckham, Nicole Bellamy, Alison Bernstein, Diane Best, Sheila Biddle, Janice Biggs, Stephanie Black, Kalifa Sobrino Bonnivier, St. Clair Bourne, Fabienne Bouville, Walter Broadnax, J. Lawrence Aber, David L. Brown, Patty Burness, Betsy Campbell, Lucille Carra, John E. Carter, Holly Carter, Penny Cass, Eric Cato, John Columbus, Adelaide Cromwell, Jimmy S. Currey, Peter Darrow, Esther R. Dyer, Nicola Ebenau, Lee Edwards, John M. Eger, Katherine Eisner, Michael Farrell, Linda Fingerson, John Fercsey, Sally Jo Fifer, Shepard Forman, Robert Franklin, Sandie de Freitas, Jon Funabiki, Mason Funk, Mary Gage-Los, Peter Geithner, Sarah George, Daniel J. Gibby, Mark Gore, William Greaves, Colin Greer, Jonathan Gruber, Slawomir Grunberg, Joyce Harnden, Laszlo Hege, Margaret Hempel, Gijs Hillenius, Ronald Howard, Tom Howe, R. J. Johnson, Gayle Anne Kelley, Jim Kennedy, Sharlene Kennedy, Martha M. Keys, Vivian Kleiman, Kay Koplovitz, Philip LaGree, Joe Lambert, Bob Larsen, Aaron Levine, Beverly Levine, Delano E. Lewis, Cheryl Larson, James Lipscomb, Jenny Lo, Henri Lopes, Luis Luna-Rosado, Theodora Lurie, Siven Maslamoney, Louis Massiah, Christian Mitchell, Stuart Math, Pamela May, Janice Molnar, Fran Montane, Leila McDowell, Christopher McLeod, Rebecca Nichols, Maria Nicolo, Laine Norkus, Augustus Richard Norton, Rory O'Connor, Patrick O'Heffernan, Thomas Okpaku, June K. Parisien-Randall, Kathy L. Paschal, Andrew Pearson, Janice Petrovich, Lydia L. Pontius, Ishmael Reed, Gini Reticker, Cathy Robertson, Tammy Robinson, Sherry Rockey, Victoria Rodriguez-Thiessen, Rob Rooy, Lorna Janet Ryan, Carolyn Sachs, Stephen Salyer, Rosalind Schneider, Anna E. Schoenfeld, Pippa Scott, Audrey Simon, Audrey Simon, Marcia Smith, Steven Smith, Jennifer Speed, Cynthia A. Stevens, Joel Sucher, Philomena Taylor, Pamela Thomas, Stacy Twilley, Christine Vincent, Parminder Vir, Christopher Walker, Allison West, Maggie Hadleigh-West, Thomas Winship, Andrew Wyndham, Cindy Young
  - 1996 Correspondence, 1996 January-March (Box 57, Folder 712-713)
    Lynn Adler, Michael Almond, George Autry, Steven Ascher, Max Anderson, John Badenhorst, Sharyn Bahn, Randy Baker, Mitchell Bard, Joanne R. Bauer, Precious S. Benson, Kate Billings, Robert Bjorklund, Andrew Blau, Claudia Bonn, Timothy Bork, Dennis Britton, Margaret Bruen, Daun Burk, Cyndie Burkhardt, Leonard Burrello, Pamela Calvert, Jeff Chester, Janet Cole, Charlotte Cole, Jacquelyn Cornish, Mark Cottrell, Judy Crichton, Robert Curvin, Stephen Curwood, Julio DaSilva, Silvina Dieguez, Dalia Diaz, Kenneth R. Donow, Pamela Esler, Maria Escobedo, David Freeman, Kathy Fredricks, Sally Jo Fifer, T. Ethelyn Fennell, Steven Fischler, Jerry Franklin, Barry Gaberman, Rob Gardner, Peter Geithner, George Gerbner, Robert Glidden, Barbara Gottschalk, Chris Greene, Rhoda Grauer, Alan E. Green, Richard Gordon, William Greaves, Henry Hampton, Arthur J. Hansen, Willis Hardshorn, Don Hazen, Christopher Hird, Julian Crandall Hollick, Josephine Holz, Roland Homet, Craig Impink, Kathleen Hall Jamieson, Lillian Jimenez, Michael Johnathon, Larry Kirkman, Hal Kirn, Avon Kirkland, Polly Kosko, Vivian Kleiman, Bunny Lester, Alan Lipke, Teresa M. Lozeau, Robert Lamb, Delano Lewis, Marion Lipschultz, Janice Molnar, Wayne Manzo, Lawrence Mullen, Cornelius Moore, Len Morris, Julianne Malveaux, Louis Massiah, John Merrow, John Richardson Meadows, Gayle McIntosh, Harold J. Marioneaux, Julianne Malveaux, NBT Productions, Sam Newbury, Patricia M. Norris, Peter Norton, Joanne Omang, Jeffrey Olson, Beverly Oliver, Judith O'Connor, Patty Powers, Judith Pemby, Gail Pellett, Drummond Pike, David Poindexter, Elana Yonah Rosen, Robin Romano, C. Wayne Rice, Jenny Richards, Robert Redford, Eric Roberts, Francis Reid, Stephanie and Charles Reinhart, Sherry Rockey, Werner Rogers, Peter Rosset, Jose Luis Ruiz, Julia Schachter, Seeds of Peace, Steve Salyer, Carolyn Sachs, Erna Smith, Dobbs Scott, Ron Schiffman, Ellen Schneider, Hedrick Smith, Robin Smith, Jenny Stevens, Joel Sucher, Lisa Seidenberg, Michael Seltzer, Southern Oregon State College, Elisa Scatena, Marcia Smith, Sally Taylor, Ruth Minster Tousson, Lisa Tait, Gennise Wilson, Sheila Walker, Charles A. Wood, Anne Walker, Marie Wilson, Stanley S. Zeitlin, Susan Yannetti, Cindy Young, Stanley Zuckerman, Mary Zurbuchen
  - 1996 Correspondence, 1996 April-June (Box 57, Folder 714, Box 58, Folder 715)
    Alan Adelson, Alyssa Hope Altschul, Rebecca M. Alvin, Jan Ames, Anita Anand, Johanna Antes, G. Asha, Katherine Ashe, David A. Baker, Henry Becton, Anita Bennett, Chip Benson, Alison Bernstein, Regine Beyer, Sheila Biddle, Terry Black, Luanne C. Bole-Becker, Michael J. Bova, Emily Breer, Nana Arhin Brempong, Jeff Brixey, Alexandra Branyon, Cheryl Brown, Christene Browne, Jillian Bullock, Frank L. Casey, Hugo Cassirer, Eric Cato, E. Samantha Cheng, Elena Chernyavskaya, Linda R. Christenson, Thomas Ciesielka, Kenneth Clark, Pamela N. Clark, Elizabeth Cohen, Lynn A. Curtis, Tania Cypriano, Reno Dakota, Caryn Davis, Jovita L. De Loatch, Susan Delson, Jon Denison, Ailyn Diaz, Dave Donnelly, Anne Drew, Ann Dunbar, Richard Dunbar, Rita Dyson, John Evans, Randa Fares, Eugene Ferraro, Sally Fifer, Heather Finnegan, Jeanne Marie Fitzsimmons, Jennifer Fox, Joel Freedman, Will Furman, Gladys Garcia, Nina F. Gibans, Michael G. Gilligan, Mark Glazman, Carolyn Goodman, Anura Goonasekara, Phil Gorn, Janet Graham, Tim Green, Harold Greenburg, Dane Griffin, Herbert Grimes II, Joan Grossman, Sheldon Hackney, Helene E. Hagan, Barbara Hall, Gillian Hazell, Margaret Hempel, Christie Herring, Sheila Hodge, Martha Hoffheimer, John C. Hogan, David Hoppe, Don Hughes, Ron Hull, Charlayne Hunter-Gault, Craig Impink, Samuel C. Inglese, Barbara Ireland, Laura Jackson, Steve James, Rosemary Jenseth, John Junkerman, Martin S. Kaplan, Carol Kimball, Mary Beth Kirchner, Larry Kirkman, Richard Knight, Scholastique Kompaore, Polly S. Kosko, Azarra Lanteri, Kalahari Family, Tod Solomon Lending, Bunny Lester, Mark Little, Saad Lounes, Beneria Lourdes, Richard L. Loveless, John Lynch, Greg Madsen, Shirley Malcom, JoAnna Baldwin Mallory, Wayne E. Manzo, John Marshall, Louis Massiah, William May, Amy Mereson, Karin Muller, Donald McHenry, David McMullin, Jeffrey B. Natt, Stanley Nelson, Ghia Nodia, Bruce Orenstein, John C. Owens, Gabrielle Palmer, Julia Parker, Milbry Catherine Polk, John R. Postill, Arleigh Prelow, Cynthia Reeves, Rebecca Rice, Richard Robinson, Sharon Percy Rockefeller, David Rodriquez, David Roland, Jose Luis Ruiz, Jeff Rush, Charlotte Ryan, William Ryerson, Barry A. Schwartz, John B. Schwatrz, Joshua Seftel, Ann Sibley, Alan Silverbach, Connie Sobczak, Frank Xaver Surth, Julia Taft, Llynn Taylor, Victor Teich, Tom Thieding, Elizabeth Thoman, Franklin A. Thomas, Thomas G. Timmreck, Mustapha Tlili, Deirdre Towers, Michael J. Tramis, Catherine Verret, Rev. Charles Walker, Anthony Wally, Anne Watson, Roger Weisberg, Dr. Kim Witte, Rabbi Amiel Wohl, Diane Wood, Kojo Yankah, Christine A. Zephirin, Frank Zuniga
  - 1996 Correspondence, 1996 July-August (Box 58, Folder 716-717)
    Kathleen Barnes, Mary Beal, Bill Berger, Gregg Biggs, Maria Blackman, Wayne Bowen, Robert G. Brzyski, Shakti Butler, Adelita Chirino, Maxi Cohen, Patrick Cozier, Marilyn Cristofori, Laini Dakar, Jason Jack Davies, Peter Davis, Susan Erenrich, Arit Essien, Verona Fonte, Phyllis D. Geeslin, Alana J. Gentry, Stephen B. Goddard, Shohihi Ghosh, Ray Grist, Lawrence K. Grossman, Shawn Hainsworth, Elaine S. Harding, Redawaan Hendricks, Fran Henry, Prudence Hill, Jeffrey Horne, Roger House, Al Hulsen, Reverend Ernest E. Hunt, Al-Yasha Ilhaam, Judy Irving, Essence Music Festival, Laura Jackson, Jason Janulis, Franmarie Kennedy-Keel, Patricia Khayyam, Polly Kosko, D. Bambi Kraus, Nathan Lachenmeyer, Debra R. Lamb, Magnus Lanje, Margaret Lazarus, Leonard Levin, Bill Lichtenstein, Katja Liendgens, JoAnna Baldwin Mallory, B.J. Mason, Michelle A. Materre, Peter Meisen, Corky Merwin, John Miles, Mark Moidel, Jon Funabiki, Richard Muller, Jean M. Mudge, David Dent McMullin, Yvette Neisser, Aaron F. Nmungwun, Dan Noyes, Steven Okazinki, Melvin Oliver, Cynthia Perry, Janice Petrovich, Johanna Pfaelzer, Sandra Polizos, Carole Punt, Rosemarie Reed, George Rios, Sanoma Robertson, Robert Rosen, Josh Ryan, William N. Ryerson, Canyon Sam, Mariana Sanchez-de-Antunano, Fred Scilpp, Ralph Screnci, Nina Gilden Seavey, Cathy Shomstein, Jo Smith, Alan Snitow, Ross Spears, Eric V. Tait, Patricia Twohill, Nikos Valance, Judith Vecchione, Teryl Watkins, Tom Weidlinger, Roger Weisberg, Tracy Western, J. Joshua Wheeler, Christal Whelan, Valerie F. Wilkerson, Virginia Williams, Clark Worswick, Lise Yasui, Orley Ben Yosef